[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the Tasmanian devil do when it feels stressed or threatened?", "correct_answer": "It produces a strong odour", "incorrect_answers": ["It starts screaming", "It plays dead", "It attacks"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When was the first fountain pen invented?", "correct_answer": "1883", "incorrect_answers": ["1902", "1906", "1887"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Blazing Saddles, in the middle of Lili Von Shtupps show, a man intrudes onto the stage. What did Lili Von Schupp do to him?", "correct_answer": "She kneed him in his private parts.", "incorrect_answers": ["She head butted him.", "She shot him.", "She kissed him."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mammary glands are considered to be modified sweat glands.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Nutritionally, eggs are considered a good source of what?", "correct_answer": "Protein", "incorrect_answers": ["Vitamin C", "Fiber", "Niacin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following do they  NOT eat a lot in Camelot according to the movie Monty Python and the Holy Grail?", "correct_answer": "Lamb", "incorrect_answers": ["Spam", "Jam", "Ham"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What color are the tights the lead singer is wearing in one of the freecreditreport.com commercials?", "correct_answer": "green", "incorrect_answers": ["yellow", "brown", "blue"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What hobby did Academy Award-winning actor Sean Connery have when he was younger?", "correct_answer": "Bodybuilding", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Car racing", "Painting"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to the Bible, Eve was made out of which of Adams bones?", "correct_answer": "Rib", "incorrect_answers": ["Tibia", "Rhombus", "Clavicle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year was the soundtrack for the movie Black Dog released?", "correct_answer": "1998", "incorrect_answers": ["1997", "1999", "1996"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the Terminator movies was voted the eighth greatest science fiction movie in history by the American Film Institute in 2008?", "correct_answer": "Terminator 2: Judgment Day", "incorrect_answers": ["Terminator Salvation", "The Terminator", "Terminator 3: Rise of the Machines"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jupiter has been called the vacuum cleaner of the Solar System.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]